Last month's GitHub didn't work at all.
The SLA is decreasing below 85% which is
crazy because the advertising like 99%.
So it's what are you doing? What are you
doing? Even Even we have better SLA and
we're just one guys. Yeah, GitHub is not
working. SLA is garbage and the old
developers are not really working on it
anymore. And at the same time, OpenAI is
releasing cool features, the slashgo
commands that can run a loop with codeex
5.5. So, can we rebuild GitHub and
rewrite every big software AI with
codeex loops? That's what we are going
to talk about right now.
>> But did you test the SLGO function?
>> Yes. So, I did I I did like two
scaffolding for different project and
even on genfit and ship code. I tried it
to prepare the build for production and
uh yeah it run both for 1 hour. Did was
I happy with the output? I don't even
remember.
>> Then it wasn't too good.
>> Yeah, it was just it run for 1 hour but
for another project like from scratch I
run this goal and then it run like a
codeex XI on it. Yeah, I was correct.
5.5 XI with the goal and it run again
for another hour and it makes some good
progress on the scaffolding that was
cleaner than before because every step
the difference is like every step it
post it checked and then it continue to
the nest. So there is some yeah loop of
testing inside this comment that it
makes it like valuable.
>> How does it decide when to stop
>> when it has the proof of the goal?
>> Okay. So instead of planning you are
just writing a full planning for your
goal.
>> Yeah. So for example for you like
because you have all of the plan and you
have like four different planes revised
like five times you will also have the
acceptance criteria of the goal inside
the specs and then you run that and if
it's reach the acceptance criteria then
you have it.
>> Yeah because I see a lot of people
saying hey like like we said before
build me a SAS I want to sell a GitHub
competitor at SLGO do it. I don't think
that's going to work. You need to still
do a proper planning with all the steps.
>> Yeah. I mean, and yeah, you still like
it can't work like that anyway.
>> It's not like magical.
>> Yeah, exactly. Because like Okay. Yeah.
It's like makes no mistake. You have a
IQ of 1,000. It's too vague. Were you
impacted by the pull request issues?
>> No, I had it like a few times that in
the evening I wanted to push and it
said, "Yeah, it's not possible." Well, I
just waited until the next morning and I
pushed my code. That's it.
>> But imagine like working with like a
team of like thousand of people and you
can't push your update, your pull
request gets squashed and what?
>> Yeah. Well, that's another one. If you
have so many people in your company
depending on the software from an
external company, then you need a
backup. Then you need like an Atlassian
server, a git bucket, I don't know, just
have a secondary setup that just can
keep on going. But you don't want like
do you really want a secondary g
repository stuff like
>> are you really going to trust GitHub an
external company with all the code and
your entire company?
>> I mean yes I don't I never work for
corporate [__] So
>> yeah it's like a bottleneck.
>> Dan, hey what's the plan? We're going to
talk about the recent GitHub outage and
what it means for free AI and if we can
and if we should even rewrite them
anyway because there is a lot of big
companies like that that have legacy
code like for example all of the bank
system like you have a cobalt
architecture are you going to rewrite it
thanks to AI
>> well first you need to find a deaf who
writes it
>> but I mean you can because they're
probably dead
>> yeah so you can't fully trust an AI how
are you going to debug it test it check
it because for a bank that's like a big
impact if you have a bug.
>> Yes. But okay. So Okay. Okay. So how
would you rewrite a bank system? What
would you do? Like cobalt is a language
from the 70s that is probably like
everyone. So ether like you have you can
hire either like 10 guys in the world
writing cobalt still today.
>> Yeah.
>> Like $2 billion a year to rewrite to
software. But then like you you you're
gonna pay those guys. It's gonna be so
expensive that it's not even worth to to
do the rewrite anyway because it works.
You just need to maintain it, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. And if it works, you don't
touch it.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
>> Eventually, you need one.
>> Yeah.
>> And you want to keep updating because
what if AI finds a bug or or a leak in
Cobalt.
>> Exactly. Which is like what what
happened with me when they found issue
with OpenBSD. Right. So even like it's
almost a requirement to rewrite you 10
years old even without talking about
like bank system right but you have
Salesforce 80 billion line of codes are
they going to rewrite the software with
AI
>> well I don't see anyone else doing it
because how are you going to write
rewrite that much code
>> an AI agent just destroy our production
data it come writing yesterday afternoon
an AI coding agent running entropy
flagship opus 4.6 deleted a production
database and all volume level backup in
a single API call to a railway or
infrastructure provider. That's a vibe
coding tech stack.
>> Yeah. Well, first question, why are you
coding with an AI agent and a production
server?
>> Because it's way simpler, bro.
>> No, I I gave like SSH access to my
production server to close to like
restart a container. Yeah, I'm not
running a like I think he's making like
a couple of million in revenue. Maybe I
will stop doing that when I generate 1
million from genfit for sure.
>> Maybe we can give a tip to the viewers
who hire devs. If your dev says, I have
this awesome function. I can SSH into
your server and use Opus to real time
change stuff so you can see it
instantly. Don't trust him.
>> Yeah,
>> you don't want to do that.
>> Yeah. Or prompt confirm before doing
anything or something like that. No.
Does that work for you?
>> No.
>> Like if if you ask to confirm before an
action, it doesn't like ask for
confirmation.
>> Sometimes not always.
>> Okay.
>> It's not possible to do it in 2 minutes
and just copy paste everything. You need
to think about what you're doing.
>> Oh, no. Exactly. And it's not working
like it's still buggy. You So you need
to py yourself. It will change something
and put it like right instead of and you
ask for left. Like you can't trust code.
Close is the coworker you have that you
have to work with. So GitHub still have
some hope stay whatever
>> they need to scale up and need to
perform better.
>> Yeah, that's sad. Okay, so should we
conclude?
>> Yes, tell us what are you going to do?
>> Mostly are we are we are we going to
rewrite GitHub with Codex? Maybe not.
>> Maybe not.
>> And that's it. Bye.
>> Thank you for watching.
>> Are we going to see all of the big
companies rewrite their software, their
tech stack to at the agent age? I don't
know. Right.
>> Yeah. And do they even need to rewrite
it? I I think they will just keep on
building new functionality and if you
just keep on scaling that part, it will
just replace it instead of rebuilding
it.
>> Yeah. Okay. And improve it. So yeah,
don't don't if it's not broken, don't
fix it. And don't replace by AI code.
>> Yeah. And just keep on building for the
next part.
>> Let's go. Okay. Thank you everyone for
watching this video. Thank you for
watching the live stream. And yeah,
we'll see you next week. Subscribe. I
watch the reals. Thank you for your
time. I love the chat the chithat even
if like I be completely brain shot.
>> Thank you and enjoy your week.